I will discuss about Microsoft 365 admin center.
When you are going to Office.com, first of all, you can see we are receiving an notification
which says the Office app is becoming a new Microsoft 365 app.
So you're home to find, create and share your content and ideas.
So when you are going to Office.com, you can see we have, for example, when I click more,
you can see we have all the different apps here, but we also have the admin center.
So the Microsoft 365 admin center gives you the opportunity to manage your Microsoft 365
environment.
Here you can see we have a Microsoft 365 admin center, and you can see the home, users,
device and more.
Well, after all, it will be able to manage the 365 admin center as an admin
administrator.
Here you can see we have admin centers.
So if I click show all, you can see we have, for example, we have our security, compliance
endpoint, Azure Active Directory, exchange endpoint and teams.
And if I click all admin centers, here you can see we have some administrator centers
that we can also manage, for example, we can have, we have the Microsoft Defender ATP Office
configuration, power automate, Power BI, and more.
So to be able to have access to the Microsoft 365 admin center, definitely, you will
need a license, and also you will also need to be a global administrator.
So if I go to users, here if I click active users, you can see we have an admin center,
I have a lot of users, which of course, most of these users have been synced from my own
premises, Active Directory.
Here, for example, you can see our users name, and also the display name, and you can
set a different license, which have been assigned to the different users.
For this other moment, I'm actually using a free trial license for Microsoft, which
of course, you can just Google the Microsoft 365 in five free trial, which will also give
you the opportunity to have the enterprise and mobility, security that does the Microsoft
365 in five.
And you can see also have Azure, but you can't really subscribe for all that free license.
For example, if you just want to actually train for the Microsoft Intune, you can also
have the Intune license, and which of course you also become the global administrator
to only manage Intune license.
And here from here, for example, we can actually decide to go to, we have the endpoint
manager, Azure Active Directory, exchange, SharePoint, Teams, and more.
Well, first of all, let me go to my Billings, and here you can see when I click your products.
So at this moment, this is how the products I have at this moment, you can see we have
the Azure Active Directory premium B2 trial, the enterprise mobility plus security in five
trial on a Microsoft 365 in five trial.
So you can see that for example, for the Azure Active Directory over 100 quantity, the enterprise
mobility over 200 and 50 quantity, and also for the Microsoft 365 in five trial, I just
only have about 25 quantity, and you can see that they are going to aspire for some of
this license.
This license gives you the opportunity to be able to, I totally renew or extend your
license, why others just can't extend your license, you need to actually purchase a license.
So next, we're going to be discussing about Azure Active Directory.
[BLANK_AUDIO]